Guide to the Records of the 7th Regiment 1767-1983 (bulk 1830-1947) MS 556
New-York Historical Society
7th Regiment Records
1767-1983 (bulk 1830-1947)
New-York Historical Society
MS 556
90 Linear Feet (97 boxes; 445 volumes)
This collection documents the history and administration of the 7th Regiment of New York. The bulk of the material pertains to regimental management, organization, and events, rather than its participation in combat and other military activities. Items include orders, correspondence, financial and legal records, reports, by-laws, enlistment records, and rosters from 7th Regiment headquarters and companies. Also included is material relating to the regiment's armories (especially the Park Ave. and 66th St. location), veterans' organizations, music, athletic clubs, recreational activities, and entertainment. The collection contains numerous scrapbooks, visual materials, publications, artifacts, and ephemera. Portions of this collection relating to the Civil War have been digitized and are available to on-site researchers and to users affiliated with subscribing institutions via EBSCOhost.
Provenance
Donation by the 7th Regiment, 1948. Subsequent donations include 1961, 1964, 1968, 1972, 1977.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.)
Historical Note
Missing Title
1806 Organized in New York, in response to troubles with the British Navy, as four companies (A,B,C,D) of Artillery, assigned to the Battalion of Artillery, First Brigade.
1807-1808 Reorganized as 2d (Infantry) Battalion, 3d Regiment of Artillery, New York State Militia.
1812 Redesignated 2d Battalion, 11th Regiment of Artillery, N.Y.S.M.
1812/1814 Active duty in New York harbor forts.
1824 Adoption of name National Guards, in honor of Marquis de Lafayette (changed to National Guard in 1832).
Adoption of gray uniforms.
Declaration of intention to become a regiment.
1825/1826 Companies E,F,G, and H are added.
1826 May 6 Reorganized and redesignated as 27th Regiment of Artillery, N.Y.S.M.
1838 Co. I is formed of cavalry, designated "First Troop, National Guard."
1847 July 27 Redesignated 7th Regiment of Infantry (National Guard), N.Y.S.M.
1849 7th Regiment suppresses Astor Place riot, killing 30.
1852 7th Regiment Band is organized.
1855 Engineers Corps is organized, titled Co. K in 1860.
1857 The 7th quells two riots, one involving the Dead Rabbits and the Bowery Boys.
1861 April 26-June 3 Mustered into federal service.
1862 June 19-Sept. 5 Mustered into federal service in Baltimore.
1862 New York State Militia redesignated New York National Guard.
1863 June 17-July 21 Mustered into federal service in Baltimore and Frederick, MD. Regiment called to New York for suppression of Draft Riots in July.
1869 The 7th serves riot duty during Orange Riots.
1874 Rifle Club is formed, regiment secures Creedmoor rifle range on Long Island.
1880 7th Regiment Armory opens on Park Avenue and 66th Street.
[1882] Camp Smith, near Peekskill, N.Y., first used for field training.
1895 Regiment on duty during Brooklyn street car strike.
Hospital Corps/ Medical Detachment is formed.
1900 Regiment called to guard duty during Croton Reservoir labor trouble.
1905/1906 Rifle matches with Queen's Westminsters.
1908 Howitzer Company formed from members of Cos. F,I, and K.
1909 Company L is formed.
1909 and 1912 7th participates in Army-National Guard maneuvers in Mass. and Conn.
1915 Supply/Service Company is formed.
1916 June 26-Dec. 2 7th mustered into federal service to guard the Mexican Border. Stationed at McAllen, TX.
1917 Aug. 5 Drafted into federal service.
1917 Oct. 1 Redesignated 107th Infantry and assigned to the 27th Division.
1917-1919 7th Infantry, New York Guard serves as Depot (Home) Battalion.
1918 27th Division is transferred to the British 4th Army. 107th Infantry engages in battles in Belgium and France; participates in assault on Hindenburg Line.
1919 Apr. 2 107th Infantry demobilized at Camp Upton, N.Y.
1921-1922 Consolidates with 7th Infantry, N.Y.G. and reorganized and federalized as 107th Infantry.
1940 Aug. 1 107th redesignated 207th Coast Artillery Anti-Aircraft.
1940 7th Regiment, N.Y. (State) Guard formed.
1941 Feb. 19 207th C.A.A.A. departs for Camp Stewart, Ga. 7th Regiment N.Y.G. occupies Armory.
1942 207th C.A.A.A. assigned to duty at Newport, R.I.
1943 April 21 Regiment broken up, reorganized and redesignated:
HQ and HQ Battery becomes HQ and HQ Battery 207th Anti-Aircraft Artillery Group
1st Battalion becomes 771st Anti-Aircraft Artillery Gun Battalion
2d Battalion becomes 7th Anti-Aircraft Artillery Automatic Weapons Battalion
3d Battalion becomes 247th Anti-Aircraft Artillery Searchlight Battalion.
1944-1945 207th ships to England, takes part in Normandy invasion. Moves into France, Luxembourg, and Germany.
7th A.A.A. Battalion serves in Pacific, on Guam, Leyte, and in the Ryukyus.
771st A.A.A. Battalion serves in Pacific at Oahu, Eniwetok, Ulithi, and Guam.
247th A.A.A. remains in U.S.
1946-1947 Consolidated, reorganized and recognized as 107th Infantry, assigned to 107th Regimental Combat Team, with HQ in New York.
1957 Relieved from 107th Regimental Combat Team, assigned to 42d Infantry Division.
1959 Relieved from 42d Infantry Division, reorganized as 107th Infantry, parent regiment under the Combat Arms Regimental System.
1993 Creation of 107th Support Group.
Prominent colonels of the 7th Regiment:
Missing Title
1859-1864 Marshall Lefferts
1864-1889 Emmons Clark
1889-1916 Daniel Appleton
Scope and Content Note
This collection documents the history and administration of the 7th Regiment of New York. The bulk of the material pertains to regimental management, organization, and events, rather than its participation in combat and other military activities. Items include orders, correspondence, financial and legal records, reports, by-laws, enlistment records, and rosters from 7th Regiment headquarters and companies. Also included is material relating to the regiment's armories (especially the Park Ave. and 66th St. location), veterans' organizations, music, athletic clubs, recreational activities, and entertainment. The collection contains numerous scrapbooks, visual materials, publications, artifacts, and ephemera. Portions of this collection relating to the Civil War have been digitized and are available to on-site researchers and to users affiliated with subscribing institutions via EBSCOhost. Material documenting the regiment's military service includes reports and rosters from the Depot (Home) Battalion, 7th Infantry who defended the Pleasantville, NY aqueduct in 1917. Items relating to World War I can be found in Company F's files in Series II, including orders, memos, bulletins, and schedules. World War I Ephemera in Series IX contains instructional, promotional and recruitment material. In addition, numerous WWI posters are located in Visual Materials. The collection also contains correspondence, personnel, publications, clippings, visual materials, and a scrapbook pertaining to the 7th Regiment's service on the Mexican border, while stationed at McAllen, Texas in 1916. Other military documentation includes a brief account of the regiment's participation in quelling the Astor Place Riots, scrapbooks relating to 1909 and 1912 war game maneuvers, and visual materials depicting camp life. Material on military training and instruction can be found in the headquarters and Francis Landon series. Civil War material includes enrollment lists found in Personnel (Series I), a number of photographs and photo albums in Visual Materials (Series XIV), and two diaries in Histories (Series VII): an anonymous diary describing training at Camp Scott on Staten Island in 1860, and a copy of Alexander Shaler's diary as a prisoner of war in 1864. There is little or no material regarding the 7th Regiment's participation in suppressing the 1863 Draft Riots. Throughout its history, the 7th Regiment's military designation changed several times (see historical note). Folder titles reflect the various identities of the regiment, when applicable. The arrangement of the 7th Regiment Records partially follows military entities, particularly headquarters and company material. Items from military levels higher than regiment, such as division or brigade, can be found in the headquarters series. Additional descriptive notes are included at the Series level.
Arrangement
The 7th Regiment Records are arranged into the following sixteen series:
Missing Title
Series I: Headquarters, 1767-1970
Series II: Companies, 1806-1949
Series III: Depot (Home) Battalion/Aqueduct Service, 1916-1929
Series IV: Francis D. Landon, 1908-1918
Series V: Robert M. Lester, 1942-1951
Series VI: Armory, 1860-1888
Series VII: Histories, 1831-1956
Series VIII: Scrapbooks, 1852-1946
Series IX: Ephemera, 1820-1976
Series X: Music, 1862-1952
Series XI: Recreational Activities, 1873-1950
Series XII: Library, 1860-1940
Series XIII: Publications, 1811-1976
Series XIV: Visual Materials, 1806-1983
Series XV: Maps, 1912-1948
Series XVI: Artifacts, 1806-1961
Related Material at The New-York Historical Society
The N-YHS Library's holdings include nearly 4,000 titles from the 7th Regiment Military Library, as well as numerous other items by or about the 7th Regiment.
Maps.; Lantern slides.; Photographs.; Dog tags.; Letter books.; Correspondence.; Camp Merritt (N.J.); McAllen (Tex.); Pleasantville (N.Y.); New York (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs.; Regiments -- 7th New York State Militia.; World War, 1939-1945 -- New York (State); World War, 1914-1918 -- Texas.; World War, 1914-1918 -- New York (State); Soldiers -- New York (State) -- New York -- Portraits.; Riot control.; Astor Place Riot, New York, N.Y., 1849; Orders (military records); Rosters.; Scrapbooks.; Bylaws.; Financial records.; Legal documents.; Sheet music.; Posters.; Ephemera.; Menus.; Tickets.; Flags.; Appleton, Daniel.; Clark, Emmons, 1827-1905.; Landon, Francis G., 1859-1947.; Lefferts, Marshall, 1821-1876.; Lester, Robert M. (Robert MacDonald), 1889-1969.; Seventh Regiment Armory.; Seventh Regiment Military Library.; United States. Army. New York Infantry Regiment, 7th (Militia), (1806-1922)
- Series I: Headquarters, 1767-1972, 13040
  Scope and Contents note
  The Headquarters series consists of materials relating to the organization and management of the regiment as a whole. The series is divided into types of material including orders, correspondence and letterbooks, financial material, legal material, training material, and minutes and reports. The series also includes material on the Committees and Board of Officers, personnel information, and material from Veterans organizations of the 7th Regiment.
  The Headquarters series contains some materials from military rankings higher than the regiment level. These include materials from the New York State Guard, as well as divisions, and brigades. These can be found within the subseries of types of material such as orders, correspondence, etc.
  - Subseries 1: Orders, 1813-1947, 13329
    The orders are organized by recipient. The regimental orders consist of special, training, parade, post, and regular orders and are organized chronologically. Orders to the New York State Guard and different divisions, brigades, and battalions are also in this series, placed after the regimental orders. In the bound orders, many circulars are also included. Note that orders directed to companies are with the companies series.
    - Eleventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1813-1820; 13393 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Eleventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1821-1823; 13392 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Eleventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1824 Jan.-1825 Jan.; 13391 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Second Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1825 Feb.-1825 Sept.; 13390 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Twenty-Seventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1826 May-1827 Dec.; 13389 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Twenty-Seventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1828-1829; 13388 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Twenty-Seventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1830-1839; 13387 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Twenty-Seventh Regiment New York State Artillery- Regimental Orders, 1840 June-1847 July; 13386 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Seventh Regiment New York State Militia (National Guard)- Regimental Orders, 1847 July-1854 Dec.; 13385 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Seventh Regiment New York State Militia (National Guard)- Regimental Orders, 1855-1861; 13384 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Seventh Regiment New York State Militia (National Guard)- Regimental Orders, 1862 Jan.-1864 Feb.; 13383 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1864 Mar.-1869 Dec.; 13382 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1870-1877; 13381 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1878-1892; 13380 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1897-1905; 13379 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1906 Jan.-1909 Jan.; 13378 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1909 Feb.-1911 Dec.; 13377 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Seventh Regiment National Guard N.Y.- Regimental Orders, 1912 Jan.-1916 May; 13376 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 107th Infantry- Regimental Orders, 1921-1949; 13375 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 7th Regiment NYG- Regimental Orders, 1946; 13374 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 42nd Infantry Division- Regimental Orders, 1947; 13373 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Headquarters of the Army- Orders, 1861-1862; 13372 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Headquarters of the Army- General Orders and Circulars (bound), 1892-1894; 13371 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - War Department- Orders, 1861-1862, 1918, 1926; 13370 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Department of the South- Orders, 1862; 13369 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - State of New York Headquarters- Orders, 1825-1827, 1850-1912; 13368 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - State of New York Division of Military and Naval Affairs- Orders, 1940 Jan.-1940 Sept.; 13367 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - State of New York Division of Military and Naval Affairs- Orders, 1940 Sept.-1940 Dec.; 13366 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Headquarters New York Guard (State Guard)- Orders, 1943-1947; 13365 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - New York State Artillery- Division Orders, 1825; 13364 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Second Division New York State Artillery- Division Orders, 1826-1827; 13363 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - First Division New York State Artillery/Militia- Division Orders, 1832-1864; 13362 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - First Division NGSNY- Division Orders, 1870-1874; 13361 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - First Brigade New York State Artillery- Brigade Orders, 1820-1849; 13360 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Sixth Brigade New York State Artillery- Brigade Orders, 1826-1827; 13359 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Third Brigade New York State Militia- Brigade Orders, 1848-1879; 13358 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Battalion Orders, 1825-1826; 13357 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 1st Brigade NY State Artillery/ 11th Regiment North Battery Garrison Orders, 1814 Aug. 31-1814 Oct. 13; 13356 (Volume 1)
    - 1st Brigade NY State Artillery/ 11th Regiment North Battery Garrison Orders, 1814 Aug. 31-1814 Oct. 13; 13355 (Volume 2)
    - 27th Regiment Orderly Book, Division, Brigade, and Regimental Orders, 1825-1827; 13354 (Volume 3)
    - 27th Regiment- General Orders, 1838-1845; 13353 (Volume 4)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1864-1869; 13352 (Volume 5)
    - 7th Regiment- General Orders, 1866-1872; 13351 (Volume 6)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1870-1873; 13350 (Volume 7)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1872-1882; 13349 (Volume 8)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1874-1877; 13348 (Volume 9)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1878-1880; 13347 (Volume 10)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1879-1881; 13346 (Volume 11)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1880 Jan. 6-1880 Feb. 10; 13345 (Volume 12)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Special Orders, 1880-1886; 13344 (Volume 13)
    - Index to 7th Regiment Special Orders, 1880-1886; 13343 (Volume 14)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1881-1884; 13342 (Volume 15)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1885-1889; 13341 (Volume 16)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1886-1891; 13340 (Volume 17)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders, 1890-1894; 13339 (Volume 18)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- General Orders and Circulars, General Headquarters, Headquarters Brigade, Headquarters 7th Regiment, 1903-1904; 13338 (Volume 19)
    - 7th Regiment General Infantry- General Orders, 1912-1916; 13337 (Volume 20)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Special Orders, 1866-1884; 13336 (Volume 21)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Special Orders, 1870-1879; 13335 (Volume 22)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard S.N.Y.- Standing Orders, 1852, 1855, 1860, 1861; 13334 (Volume 23)
    - 14th N.Y. State Artillery (Governor's Guard), 1820-1831; 13333 (Volume 24)
    - 3rd Brigade Infantry- Orderly Book, 1814; 13332 (Volume 25)
    - 7th Regiment, 2nd Company (1849-1857); 3rd Regiment NYSA (1846-1847), Company B and Company H; 8th Regiment NYSM (1847-1848), 1846-1857; 13331 (Volume 26)
    - Adjutant General, Divisional, and General Orders, 1882-1884; 13330 (Volume 27)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence, 1819-1951, 13299
    The regimental correspondence is arranged chronologically. It is mostly incoming correspondence to the regiment, but some copies and carbon copies of outgoing correspondence are included. Some letters to the Board of Officers and correspondence among soldiers and officials of the 7th Regiment are also included. Most of the correspondence documents routine matters such as invitations to dinners and events, resignations, elections of officers, parades, uniforms, and the use of the armory. Events such as the Astor Place Riots, the Draft Riots, the Civil War, and World War I are not represented in the correspondence. However, some letters from 1916 from McAllen, Texas detail the camp conditions and the attitude of the men while guarding the Mexican Border.
    The letterbooks contain the correspondence of Colonel Appleton and Colonel Clark which detail the administrative management of the regiment. The letterbook of Philip Rhinelander contains correspondence regarding his collecting of Civil War relics.
    - Correspondence, 1819-1847; 13328 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1850-1859; 13327 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1860-1869; 13326 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1870-1879; 13325 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1881-1885; 13324 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1886-1889; 13323 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1890-1896; 13322 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1900-1909; 13321 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1911-1916; 13320 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1919; 13319 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1920-1925; 13318 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1926-1929; 13317 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1930-1935; 13316 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1940-1951; 13315 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Undated; 13314 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, 1875-1880; 13313 (Volume 28)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Clark, 1867-1875; 13312 (Volume 29)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Clark, 1867-1872; 13311 (Volume 30)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Clark, 1886-1889; 13310 (Volume 31)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Clark, 1880-1886; 13309 (Volume 32)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Appleton, Vol. 1, 1891-1892; 13308 (Volume 33)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Appleton, Vol. 2, 1892-1894; 13307 (Volume 34)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Appleton, Vol. 3, 1894-1895; 13306 (Volume 35)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Appleton, Vol. 4, 1895-1897; 13305 (Volume 36)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Colonel Appleton, Vol. 5, 1897-1898; 13304 (Volume 37)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, C.F. Robbin, 1868; 13303 (Volume 38)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Louis B. Radar, 1879-1881; 13302 (Volume 39)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Philip Rhinelander, 1896; 13301 (Volume 40)
    - 7th Regiment Letterbook, Philip Rhinelander, 1896; 13300 (Volume 41)
  - Subseries 3: Memoranda, Notices, Circulars, 1820-1954, 13280
    This subseries consists of formal communication within the 7th Regiment that is not orders. This includes memos, circulars, and other notices to members. It also includes internal communications in the division of militia affairs of the war department, brigades, and the New York Guard.
    - Eleventh Regiment of the New York State Artillery- Memoranda, 1820; 13298 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 7th Regiment- Memoranda, 1883-1889; 13297 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 7th Regiment New York Guard (State Guard)- Memoranda, 1942-1947; 13296 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 107th and 20th Infantry- Memoranda, 1939 Jan.-1939 July; 13295 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 107th and 20th Infantry- Memoranda, 1939 July-1940 April; 13294 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 107th and 20th Infantry- Memoranda, 1940 May-1940 Dec.; 13293 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - New York Guard (State Guard)- Memoranda, 1942-1944; 13292 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - New York Guard (State Guard)- Memoranda, 1946-1947; 13291 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 7th Regiment- Notices to Members, 1825-1954; 13290 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - War Department, Division of Militia Affairs- Circular, 1908; 13289 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 7th Regiment National Guard- Circulars, 1823-1878; 13288 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 7th Regiment NYG- Circulars, 1942-1945; 13287 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - National Guard State of New York- Circulars, 1870, 1878; 13286 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - New York Guard (State Guard)- Circulars, 1942-1948; 13285 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - First Brigade N.Y. Guard- Circular, 1944; 13284 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Department of Rifle Practice, State of New York- 1875-1878, 13283 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Inspector General's Department, State of New York- Circulars, 1878; 13282 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - New York Military Association- Circular, 1857; 13281 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 4: Board of Officers and Committees, 1833-1949, 13237
    This subseries contains material produced by the regiment's Board of Officers and its various committees. The Board of Officers material includes by-laws, resolutions, meeting minutes, minute books, and reports of the officers. The committee material is reports from various committees to the Board of Officers. The main committees of the regiment include the Armory Committee, the Committee on the Awards of the Cross of Honor, the Library and Arts Committee, and the General Committee on the New Armory. The regiment had other special committees that met for a short duration to complete a special project, such as a committee on an upcoming ball. These special committees are together in chronological order.
    - By-Laws and Changes to By-Laws of the Board of Officers, 1856-1949; 13279 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Board of Officers- Resolutions, 1833-1917; 13278 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Board and Council of Officers- Meeting Minutes, 1860-1861; 13277 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Board of Officers- Roster, 1879; 13276 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Board of Officers- Treasurer's Reports, 1863-1869; 13275 (Box 7, Folder 15)